#### Contact

179 South Avenue New Canaan, CT 06840 USA 203-966-4880 (Work) susan@susanbaker.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ susankeanebaker (LinkedIn) www.susanbaker.com (Company)

#### Top Skills

Patient Experience
Public Speaking
HCAHPS

# Susan Keane Baker

Supporting you and improving patient experience and HCAHPS scores via engaging webinars, courses and books.

**New Canaan** 

# Summary

Are your patients enjoying exceptional patient experiences?

Is your team receiving glowing praise in patient surveys and on social media? Does every member of your team feel like they are making a difference?

All of my work experience is in healthcare, which means that I understand the need for practical approaches that can be implemented quickly. Chief experience officers, chief nursing officers, and healthcare leaders look to me for virtual meetings and webinars on these topics:

- Managing Patient Expectations
- How to Create Quick Rapport When Time is Limited
- Skills for the Busiest Leadership Teams
- You Can Soothe, Smooth & Improve Difficult People

It's been my pleasure to speak for:

- -American Academy of Family Physicians
- -American Association of Occupational Health Nurses
- -American College of Gastroenterology
- -American Medical Association
- -American Society for Healthcare Risk Management
- -Ardent Health Services
- -Arkansas Hospital Association
- -Arizona Hospital and Healthcare Association
- -Association of Administrators of Academic Pediatrics
- -Association of American Veterinary Medical Colleges
- -Avatar Solutions

And that's just a few of the A's...

If you are a healthcare leader who needs a quality improvement initiative that really matters to patients, consider my virtual course, Telephone Rapport. It's not your typical telephone etiquette program. Telephone Rapport is an on-the-job micro-learning experience that layers in behaviors to improve patient satisfaction while reducing the length of most calls. Improvements are sustained via the easy-to-implement Telephone Rapport Peer Coaching Program that is included with the course.

Take the next steps to improve patient experience:

- Book me for a webinar or highly interactive virtual meeting with your team.
- Purchase Telephone Rapport for improved patient experiences from Day 1.
- Sign up at www.susanbaker.com to receive (free) "Caring Minute."

203-966-4880 or susan@susanbaker.com

## Experience

Higher HCAHPS Scores: The Willing to Recommend Approach Author and speaker July 1994 - Present (26 years 2 months)

Greenwich Hospital
Speaker on Patient Experience
September 1998 - October 2015 (17 years 2 months)
Greenwich Connecticut USA

Malcolm Baldrige National Quality Award Member, Board of Examiners 2008 - 2011 (3 years)

### Education

College of the Holy Cross BA, Liberal Arts

State University of New York at Stony Brook MHA, Hospital Administration